A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Librarian of Virginia, 1832-2024 Jan
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and Subject Files, 1827-2007.
  - 1903-1968 (Accession 28078)., 72.45 (212 boxes)
    - Mi, 1934 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Mo-Mz, 1934 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Mc, 1935 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - M-Me, 1935 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Mi, 1935 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Mo-Mu, 1935 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Mc, 1936 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Ma, 1936 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Me-Mi, 1936 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Mo-Mu, 1936 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Mc, 1937 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - M, 1937 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Me, 1937 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Mi, 1937 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Mo-Mu, 1937 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Mc, 1938 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Ma, 1938 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Me, 1938 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Mi, 1938 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Mo-My, 1938 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Mc, 1939 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Ma, 1939 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Me, 1939 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Mi, 1939 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Mo, 1939 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Mu, 1939 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Mc, 1940 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Ma, 1940 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Me-Mu, 1940 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Mc, 1941 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Ma, 1941 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Me-Mu, 1941 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - M-Me, 1942 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Mi-My, 1942 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Ma-Me, 1943 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Mi-My, 1943 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - M, 1944 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Mc, 1945 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Ma, 1945 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Me-My, 1945 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Mc, 1946 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Ma, 1946 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Me-My, 1946 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Mc, 1947 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Ma, 1947 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Me-My, 1947 (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Mc, 1948 (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - Ma, 1948 (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - Me-My, 1948 (Box 98, Folder 18)
    - M-Me, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Mi-My, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - M-Me, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Mi-My, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - M, 1951 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - M, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - M, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - M, 1954 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - M, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - M, 1956 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - M, 1957 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - M, 1958 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - M, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - M, 1960 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - M, 1961 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - M, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - M, 1963 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - M, 1964 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - M, 1965 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - M, 1966 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - M, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - M, 1968 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Mailing List, (A-K), 1954 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Mailing List, (L-Z), 1954 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Mariner's Museum, 1934-1935 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Micro Photo Inc., 1959-1960 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Micro Photo Inc., 1961-1965 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Minutes - Library Board: Rules and Policies, 1903-1945 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Exchanges (A-C), 1934-1948 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Exchanges (D-E), 1937-1948 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Exchanges (Duplicate Lists), 1910-1941 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Exchanges (F-H) 1927-1942 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Exchanges (I), 1935-1942 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Exchanges (J-M), 1939 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Exchanges (Mailing Lists), 1936-1939 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Exchanges (N), 1936-1942 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Exchanges (North Carolina), 1934-1941 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Exchanges (O), 1937-1939 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Exchanges (Ohio), 1935-1938 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Exchanges (P), 1935-1939 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Exchanges (R-T), 1938-1941 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Exchanges (U), 1934-1942 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Exchanges (V), 1939-1941 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Exchanges (W), 1936-1942 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Exchanges (Washington), 1934-1939 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Exchanges (West Virginia), 1936-1940 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Exchanges (Y), 1934-1939 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Mural-Binford, Julien, 1950-1951 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Mural-Cheek, Leslie Jr., Director Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1950-1953 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Mural-Mimeographed Letters to Artist, 1950 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Mural-Artist's Replies, 1950 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Mural-Miscellaneous, 1950-1951 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Mural-Miscellaneous, 1951 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Mural-State Library, 1943-1946 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - N, 1905-1907 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - N, 1908 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - N, 1909 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - N, 1910 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - N, 1911 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - NE-NO, 1910-1911 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - N, 1912 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - NA-NE, 1913 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - NI-NZ, 1913 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - NA-NE, 1914 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Ne-Ny, 1914 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - N-Ne, 1915 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Ni-Ny, 1915 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - N-Ne, 1916 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - No-Ny, 1916 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - N, 1917 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Na, 1918 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Ne-Nu, 1918 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Na, 1919 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Ne-Nu, 1919 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Na, 1920 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Ne-Nu, 1920 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - N, 1921 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - N, 1922 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - N, 1923 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - N, 1923 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - N, 1924 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - N, 1925 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - N-Ne, 1926 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Ni-Nu, 1926 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - N-Ne, 1927 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - No-Ny, 1927 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - N-Ne, 1928 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Ni-Ny, 1928 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - N-Ne, 1929 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - No-Nu, 1929 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - N-Ne, 1930 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - No-Ny, 1930 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - N-Ne, 1931 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - No-Nu, 1931 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - N-Ne, 1932 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Ni-Nu, 1932 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - N-Ne, 1933 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Ni-Ny, 1933 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - N-Ne, 1934 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - No-Ny, 1934 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - N-Ne, 1935 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - No-Ny, 1935 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - N-Ne, 1936 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Ni-Nu, 1936 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - N-Ne, 1937 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Ni-Nu, 1937 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - N, 1938 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Na, 1939 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Ne-Ny, 1939 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - N, 1940 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - N, 1941 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - N, 1942 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - N, 1943 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - N, 1944 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - N, 1945 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - N, 1946 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - N-Ni, 1947 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - No, 1947 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - N-Ni, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - No, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - N, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - N-Ni, 1950 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - No, 1950 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - N, 1951 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - N, 1951 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - N, 1952 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - N, 1953 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - N, 1954 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - N, 1955 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - N, 1956 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - N, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - N, 1958 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - N, 1958 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - N, 1959 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - N, 1960 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - N, 1961 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - N, 1962 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - N, 1963 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - N, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - N, 1965 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - N, 1966 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - N, 1967 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - National Association of State Libraries-Public Archives Committee (Alabama-Connecticut), 1912-1916 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - National Association of State Libraries-Public Archives Committee (Delaware-Kentucky), 1912-1917 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - National Association of State Libraries-Public Archives Committee (Library of Congress-Louisiana-New Jersey), 1911-1918 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - National Association of State Libraries-Public Archives Committee (New York-Philippines Islands), 1911-1917 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - National Association of State Libraries-Public Archives Committee (Porto Rico-Wyoming), 1912-1917 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - National Library Week, 1957 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - National Library Week, 1958 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - National Library Week, 1959 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - O, 1903-1912 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - O, 1913-1921 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - O, 1922-1924 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - O, 1925-1927 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - O, 1928-1929 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - O, 1930-1931 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - O, 1932-1933 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - O, 1934-1935 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - O, 1936 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - O, 1937-1939 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - O, 1940-1941 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - O, 1942-1943 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - O, 1944 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - O, 1945 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - O, 1946 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - O, 1947 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - O, 1948 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - O, 1949 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - O, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - O, 1952-1954 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - O, 1955-1957 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - O, 1958-1960 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - O, 1961 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - O, 1962 (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - O, 1963 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - O, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - O, 1965 (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - O, 1966 (Box 118, Folder 19)
    - O, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 20)
    - O, 1968 (Box 118, Folder 21)
    - P, 1903-1905 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - P, 1906-1907 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - P, 1908-1909 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - P, 1910-1911 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - P, 1912-1913 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - P, 1914 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - P, 1915 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - P, 1916 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - P, 1917 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - P, 1918-1919 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - P-Pe, 1920 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Pi-Pu, 1920 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - P-Pe, 1921 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Pi-Pu, 1921 (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - P, 1922 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - P, 1923 (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - P, 1924 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - P, 1925 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - P, 1926 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - P, 1927 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - P-Ph, 1928 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Po-Py, 1928 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - P-Ph, 1929 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Pl-Py, 1929 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - P-Pe, 1930 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Pi-Py, 1930 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - P-Pe, 1931 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Ph-Py, 1931 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - P-Pe, 1932 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Ph-Py, 1932 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - P-Pe, 1933 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Ph-Py, 1933 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - P-Pi, 1934 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Po-Py, 1934 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - P-Pe, 1935 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Ph-Pl, 1935 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Po-Py, 1935 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - P-Ph, 1936 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Pl-Py, 1936 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - P-Pe, 1937 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Ph-Py, 1937 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - P-Pe, 1938 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Ph-Po, 1938 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Pr-Py, 1938 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - P-Pe, 1939 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Pi-Po, 1939 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Pr-Py, 1939 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - P, 1940 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - P, 1941 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - P, 1942 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - P-Ph, 1943 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Pi-Pu, 1943 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - P, 1944 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - P-Ph, 1945 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Pi-Pu, 1945 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - P-Pi, 1946 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Po-Pu, 1946 (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - P-Pi, 1947 (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - Po-Pu, 1947 (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - P-Pe, 1948 (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Ph-Pu, 1948 (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - P-Pe, 1949 (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - Ph-Pu, 1949 (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - P-Pe, 1950 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Ph-Py, 1950 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - P, 1951 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - P, 1952-1953 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - P, 1954 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - P, 1955-1956 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - P, 1957 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - P, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - P, 1959 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - P, 1960 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - P, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - P, 1962 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - P, 1963 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - P, 1964 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - P, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - P, 1966 (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - P, 1967 (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - P, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - Personnel, Division of, 1948-1952 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Powell, Helen, Reed 1948-1951 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Q, 1903-1929 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Q, 1930-1939 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Q, 1941-1942 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Q, 1943-1945 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Q, 1946-1961 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Q, 1965-1968 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - R, 1903-1909 (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - R, 1910-1911 (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - R, 1912-1913 (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - R, 1914-1915 (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - R, 1916-1917 (Box 128, Folder 13)
    - R, 1918-1919 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - R, 1920-1921 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - R, 1922 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - R, 1923 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - R, 1924 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - R, 1925 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - R, 1926 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - R, 1927 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - R, 1928 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - R, 1929 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - R, 1930 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - R-Ri, 1931 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Ro-Ry, 1931 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - R-Ri, 1932 (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Ro-Ry, 1932 (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - R-Ri, 1933 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Ro-Ry, 1933 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - R, 1934 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - R, 1935 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - R-Ri, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Ro-Ry, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - R-Ri, 1937 (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Ro-Ry, 1937 (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - R-Ri, 1937 (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Ro-Ry, 1938 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Ra, 1939 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Re-Ri, 1939 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Ro-Ry, 1939 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - R-Ri, 1940 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Ro-Ry, 1940 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - R-Ri, 1941 (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Ro-Ry, 1941 (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - R-Ri, 1942 (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Ro-Ru, 1942 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - R-Ri, 1943 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Ro-Ru, 1943 (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - R, 1944 (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - R-Ri, 1945 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Ro-Ru, 1945 (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - R-Ri, 1946 (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Ro-Ru, 1946 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - R-Ri, 1947 (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Ro-Ru, 1947 (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - R-Ri, 1948 (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Ro-Ry, 1948 (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - R-Ri, 1949 (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - Ro-Ry, 1949 (Box 133, Folder 14)
    - R-Ri, 1950 (Box 133, Folder 15)
    - Ro-Ru, 1950 (Box 133, Folder 16)
    - R, 1951 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - R, 1952 (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - R, 1953 (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - R, 1954 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - R, 1955-1956 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - R, 1957 (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - R, 1958 (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - R, 1959 (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - R, 1960 (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - R, 1961 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - R, 1962 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - R, 1963 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - R, 1964 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - R, 1965 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - R, 1965 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - R, 1966 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - R, 1967 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - R, 1968 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Richmond Area Community Council School Lunch Study, 1953-1954 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Richmond Area University Center, 1946-1947 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Richmond Area University Center, 1948 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Richmond Area University Center, 1949 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Richmond Area University Center, 1950-1951 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Richmond Public Library, 1953-1955 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Richmond School Board, 1947 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Richmond School Board, 1948 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Richmond School Board, 1949 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Richmond School Board, 1950 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Richmond School Board, 1951 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Richmond School Board, 1952 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Richmond School Board, 1953 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Richmond School Board Minutes, 1950-1952 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Richmond Stadium Dedications of, Minutes, 1949 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - S, 1906-1907 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - S, 1907 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - S, 1908 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - S-Sl, 1909 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Sm-Sy, 1909 (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - S-So, 1910 (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Sp-Sy, 1910 (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - S-Sn, 1911 (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - So-Sy, 1911 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - S-Sm, 1912 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Sh, 1912 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Sn-Sy, 1912 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - S-Sn, 1913 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - So-Sy, 1913 (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - S-Sm, 1914 (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Sn-Sy, 1914 (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - S-Sm, 1915 (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Sn-Sz, 1915 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - S-Sn, 1916 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - So-Sz, 1916 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - S-Sm, 1917 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Sn-Sz, 1917 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - S-So, 1918 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Sp-Sy, 1918 (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - S-Sl, 1919 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Sm-Sy, 1919 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - S-Sn, 1920 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - So-Sy, 1920 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - S-Sm, 1921 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Sn-Sy, 1921 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - S-Sn, 1922 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Sm-Sy, 1922 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - S-Sl, 1923 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Sm-Sy, 1923 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - S-Sm, 1924 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Sn-Sy, 1924 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - S-Se, 1925 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Sh-Sm, 1925 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - So-Sy, 1925 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - S-Sl, 1926 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Sm-Sr, 1926 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - St-Sy, 1926 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - S-Se, 1927 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Sh-So, 1927 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Sp-Sz, 1927 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - S-Se, 1928 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Sh-Sm, 1928 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Sn-Sr, 1928 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - St-Sz, 1928 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - S-Sl, 1929 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Sm-Sq, 1929 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - St-Sy, 1929 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - S-Sl, 1930 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Sm-Ss, 1930 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - St-Sy, 1930 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - S-Sl, 1931 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Sq-Sy, 1931 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - S-Se, 1932 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Sh-So, 1932 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Sp-Sy, 1932 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - S-Sl, 1933 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Sm-Sr, 1933 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - St-Sy, 1933 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - S-Se, 1934 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Sh-So, 1934 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Sp-Sy, 1934 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - S-Sl, 1935 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Sm-Sp, 1935 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - St-Sy, 1935 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - S-Sl, 1936 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Sm-Sp, 1936 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - St-Sy, 1936 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - S-Sl, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Sm-Sr, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - St-Sy, 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Sa-Se, 1938 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Sh-Sk, 1938 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Sm-Sr, 1938 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - St-Sy, 1938 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Sa-Se, 1939 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Sl-Sm, 1939 (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Sn-Sr, 1939 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - St-Sy, 1939 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - S-Sm, 1940 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Sn-Sy, 1940 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - S-So, 1941 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Sp-Sy, 1941 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - S-Sn, 1942 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - So-Sy, 1942 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - S-So, 1943 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Sp-Sy, 1943 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - S, 1944 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - S-Sn, 1945 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - So-Sy, 1945 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - S-Su, 1946 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Sp-Sw, 1946 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - S-Sn, 1947 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - So-Sy, 1947 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - S-So, 1948 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Sp-Sy, 1948 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - S-Sp, 1949 (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - St-Sy, 1949 (Box 151, Folder 11)
    - SA-SO, 1950 (Box 151, Folder 12)
    - SP-SY, 1950 (Box 151, Folder 13)
    - S, 1951 (Box 151, Folder 14)
    - S, 1952 (Box 151, Folder 15)
    - S, 1953 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - S, 1954 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - S, 1955 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - S, 1956 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - S, 1957 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - S, 1957 (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - S, 1958 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - S, 1959 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - S, 1960 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - S, 1960 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - S, 1961 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - S, 1961 (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - S, 1962 (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - S, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - S, 1964 (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - S, 1965 (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - S, 1966 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - S, 1967 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - S, 1967 (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - S, 1968 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Snead and Company Iron Works, 1968 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Sons of the Revolution, 1930-1931 (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Sons of the Revolution, 1931 (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Sons of the Revolution, 1932-1933 (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - Southeastern Book Purchasing Agreement, 1944-1946 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Southeastern Library Association (SELA), 1940-1941 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Southeastern Library Association (SELA), 1948 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Southeastern Library Association (SELA), 1954-1956 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Southeastern Library Association Committees-Activities Committee, 1954-1956 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Southeastern Library Association Committees-Audio Visual Committee, 1956-1958 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Southeastern Library Association Committees-Constitution Committee, 1956-1958 (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Southeastern Library Association Committees-General Committees, 1954-1958 (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Southeastern Library Association Committees-Legislation Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Southeastern Library Association Committees-Library Education Committee, 1956-1958 (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Southeastern Library Association Committees-Library Work as a Career, 1956-1958 (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Southeastern Library Association Committees-Local Arrangements, 1957-1958 (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Southeastern Library Association Committees-Nominating Committee, 1956-1958 (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - Southeastern Library Association Committees-Promotional Material Committee, 1956-1958 (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - Southeastern Library Association Committees-Reports (Committee), 1950-1952 (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - Southeastern Library Association Committees-Resource Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 155, Folder 16)
    - Southeastern Library Association-Southern Books Competition Committee, 1956-1958 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Southeastern Library Association-Dinners, 1938 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Southeastern Library Association-Executive Board Duties, 1958 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Southeastern Library Association-Executive Board Minutes and Agendas, 1955-1959 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Southeastern Library Association-Executive Secretary, 1957-1958 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Southeastern Library Association-Executive Secretary Duties, n.d. (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Southeastern Library Association-Exhibit Reservation, 1958 (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Southeastern Library Association-Exhibit Reservation, 1958 (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Southeastern Library Association-Exhibit Reservation, 1958 (Box 156, Folder 9)